No? Then why did you
throw away my flowers?
Because you didn't respect
our agreement.
I've never treated what we have
as just a contract.
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
It's boiling.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 16=
(By Reason, By Fairness, By Law,
Everything Is on Your Side)
Wow, it smells great.
Shen Gu,
about Su Mei,
thank you.
I should've told you earlier.
Here.
Try
the fish maw
and matsutake mushroom chicken soup.
Careful, it's got.
It's really good.
Have more.
How are you so good at cooking?
When I was abroad,
I missed the taste of Gang City
and the people here.
Looks like Wanxin won't be able
to have dinner with me as often anymore.
You didn't look like this
when you were pushing them together.
It finally feels real
that my granddaughter is married.
I'll spend more time with you.
There's another soup.
Li, come and sit.
Sit. Let's eat.
Do we still have that bajiu
we brought back from Shen City?
You can only have half a glass.
Alright, half a glass.
Get the bajiu.
You two are teaming up
to trick me, huh?
Didn't you say
the most dangerous place
is the safest place?
Li,
let's toast to Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu, here.
Wishing you health and happiness.
Health and happiness.
Cheers.
(Xu Wanxin)
What's up?
From today on,
I'm officially living with Shen Gu.
What?
You're living together?
Xu Wanxin,
that's great.
You like each other,
and the misunderstandings are cleared.
You're adults.
That's how it should be.
Yes, but I...
Want to have a round?
What?
Miss Song,
you can't rush
things like that.
What are you talking about?
When did I even say?
Ah?
What did I say?
What are you thinking?
Alright.
Just follow your heart.
I have no objections.
Honestly, Shen Gu
seems like a decent guy.
That's it. I'm going back to my game.
We'll talk when we meet. Bye.
Song Xi!
Did you know
Wanxin moved in with Shen Gu?
What is that?
It's going to rain.
Quick. Let's have one more round.
You
are done for.
Come on.
Alright.
I'll be fine from here.
Thank you for dinner.
I'm homeless tonight.
Also,
I don't feel like going back
to be the victim again.
I've got filming tomorrow.
Good night,
homeless man.
Good night.
I really am homeless now.
(Lawyer Fang)
♪The clouds hide the faint light
behind them♪
♪A lonely bench on the street corner♪
♪Where all feelings come to rest♪
♪In the night sky, the moon's trail♪
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
♪I search my memories with all my might♪
♪Love catches me off guard♪
♪You, in the album♪
The number you've dialed
is currently unavailable.
♪The world suddenly has meaning♪
♪Through the pouring rain, I found you♪
♪In the space of our embrace♪
♪Stars spill across the sky♪
You finally decided to pick up.
Is your phone for decoration?
Do you know how many missed calls
you have?
It was a heavy downpour.
My pillow was at your place.
I couldn't sleep
without my pillow. You know that.
Come and get it today.
That's better for both of us.
Shen Gu, I'm not a stray.
I have a home in Gang City, okay?
Morning.
Is there anything you can't do?
You'll find out slowly.
Try it.
I'll give you a ride to work.
What?
Are you thinking of kissing me
in the car again?
I was drunk. I don't remember.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪